RG 014, Department of Banking
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Receivership Files, 1918-1971; 92.5 cubic feet
  - Bank records, circa 1918-1967; 45 cubic feet
    - Merchants Trust Company, Waterbury (Box 73)
      - Legal papers (Box 73)
        - Foreclosures (Box 73)
        - Real estate owned (Box 73)
        - Court orders, 1932-1935 (Box 73)
        - Compromise settlements closed (Box 74)
        - Release of mortgage (Box 74)
        - Real estate sold (Box 74)
        - Reports (Box 74)
        - Other legal papers (Box 74)
      - Correspondence and papers (Box 74)
      - Notes to quit, 1933-1935 (Box 74)
      - Papers of the Citizens and Manufacturers National Bank of Waterbury as receiver fro the Merchants Trust Co., including letters, applications and orders, federal taxes (Box 75)
      - Special Report of Council for the Receiver, 1933 (Box 75)
      - Return of claims filed, 1932 (Box 75)
      - Inventory, 1932 (Box 75)
      - Bankruptcy papers, proofs of debt, 1932-1935 (Box 75)
      - Reports of the receiver, 1934 (Box 75)
      - Brief description of the receivership (Box 75)
      - Court orders, 1-335, 1932-1934 (Box 76)
      - Court orders, 336-1495, 1934-1935 (Box 77)
      - Legal papers (Box 78)
        - Dockets, 1931-1934 (Box 78)
        - Court orders, 1932-1934 (Box 78)
        - Claims and settlements (Box 78)
      - Files including summary of orders, 1933-1935 (Box 79)
      - List of depositors (Box 79)
      - Papers of the Citizens and Manufacturers National Bank as receiver (Box 79)
        - Reservations to the Supreme Court (Conn.), 1932 (Box 79)
        - Receiver's report, 1934-1935 (Box 79)
      - Court orders and notes written off at close of receivership, 1946-1952 (Box 80)
    - Hamden Bank and Trust Company (Box 80)
      - Miscellaneous receipts (Box 80)
      - Court orders (Box 80)
      - Notes written off (Box 80)
    - Unionville Bank and Trust Company (Box 81)
      - Legal papers (Box 81)
        - Mortgage releases (Box 81)
        - Compromise settlements closed (Box 81)
        - Reports (Box 81)
        - Judgment for receivership (Box 81)
      - Receiver's check register (Box 81)
      - Trust material (Box 81)
      - Trust files (Box 82)
    - West Haven Bank and Trust Company (Box 82)
      - Court papers, 1933-1935 (Box 82)
      - Receiver's check register (Box 83)
      - Legal papers (Box 83)
        - Real estate sold, 1936-1939 (Box 83)
        - Compromise settlements closed, 1936-1945 (Box 83)
        - Receivership termination (Box 83)
        - Reports (Box 83)
        - Application concerning sale of assets, 1945 January (Box 83)
        - Miscellaneous legal papers (Box 83)
      - Notes written off (Box 83)
      - Real estate files (Box 84)
      - Real estate files (Box 85)
      - Report of examination, 1931 May 7 (Box 85)
      - Trust material of Joseph C. Raytkivich (Box 86)
      - Correspondence (Box 86)
      - Release of mortgage, 1935-1963 (Box 86)
    - Windsor Locks Trust and Safe Deposit Company (Box 86)
      - Receiver's check register (Box 86)
      - Legal papers (Box 86)
        - Release of mortgage (Box 86)
        - Real estate sold (Box 86)
        - Compromise settlements closed (Box 86)
        - Application concerning sale of assets (Box 86)
        - Receivership termination (Box 86)
        - Judgment for receivership, 1935 September 16 (Box 86)
        - Court orders, 1943 July 1 - 1950 March 13 (Box 86)
  - Bank Records of Accounts, 1952; .5 cubic feet (29 reels)
    - American Bank and Trust Company, Bridgeport (Box 87)
      - Savings Accounts, A-O, 1952 December 22 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Savings Accounts, P-Z, 1952 December 23 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - N.P. Accts. 31 N. P. to N. P. 6950, 1952 December 23 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Industrial Accts. A50069 - A52494, 1952 December 23 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Commercial Accounts, A-I, 1952 December 30 (Box 87, Reel Roll 3)
      - Commercial Accounts, I-Z, 1952 December 30 (Box 87, Reel Roll 4)
    - Broadway Bank and Trust Company, New Haven (Box 87)
      - Checking Accts. A-Z, 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Xmas Clubs, 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Certificate of Deposit, 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Interest on Certificate of Deposit, 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Estates, 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Trust Accts., 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Certified Checks, 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Attached Accts., 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Xmas Club Checks, 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Bankrupt Accts., 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Savings Accts. - Cards and Jackets, A-Z, 1952 December 22 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
    - Citizens Bank & Trust Company, New Haven (Box 87)
      - Savings Ledger Cards & Jackets, A-Z, 1952 December 11 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Comm. Checking Accts. A-Z, 1952 December 11 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Inactive Ledger Accts. & Accts. Set off against debts, Not sorted, 1952 December 11 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
    - City Bank & Trust Company, Hartford (Box 87)
      - Checking Accounts A-Q, 1952 December 9 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Checking Accounts R-Z, 1952 December 10 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Savings Accounts A-C, 1952 December 10 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Savings Accounts D-L, 1952 December 10 (Box 87, Reel Roll 3)
      - Savings Accounts M-U, 1952 December 10 (Box 87, Reel Roll 4)
      - Savings Accounts V-Z, 1952 December 11 (Box 87, Reel Roll 5)
    - Commercial Bank and Trust Company, Bridgeport (Box 87)
      - Savings Accounts A-Z, cards and some jackets, 1952 December 23 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Commercial Accounts A-L, 1952 December 31 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Commercial Accounts M-Z, 1952 December 31 (Box 87, Reel Roll 3)
      - Certified Deposit and Checks, 1952 December 31 (Box 87, Reel Roll 3)
    - Commercial Trust Company, New Britain (Box 87)
      - Savings and Accounts $10 & under A-Z, 1952 December 16 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Savings Accounts over $10 A-R, 1952 December 16 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Savings Accounts over $10 S-Z, 1952 December 16 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Checking Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 16 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Inactive unfiled cards, 1952 December 16 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
    - East Hampton Bank & Trust Company (Box 87)
      - Checking, Savings and other, Deposit Accounts combined, Accounts are numbered, 1952 December 17 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
    - Hamden Bank and Trust Company (Box 87)
      - Checking Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 17 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Other deposits, 1952 December 17 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Over drafts, 1952 December 17 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Savings Accounts Card & Jackets, A-Z, 1952 December 17 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Unfiled Cards and Jackets, 1952 December 17 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
    - Manchester Trust and Safe Deposit Company (Box 87)
      - Checking Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 11 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
    - Mechanics Bank, New Haven (Box 87)
      - Savings Accounts, Cards & Jackets A-R, 1952 December 18 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Savings Accts. Cards & Jackets S-Z, 1952 December 18 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Paid Notes R.F.C. A-Z, 1952 December 18 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Checking Accounts A-H, 1952 December 18 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Checking Accounts I-Z - 1700, 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 3)
      - Pd. Accts. $10 & under, 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 3)
      - Certificate of Deposit Ledger, 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 3)
      - Attached Accts., 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 3)
      - Accts. Assigned to R.F.C., 1952 December 19 (Box 87, Reel Roll 3)
    - Merchants Trust Company, Waterbury (Box 87)
      - Savings Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 16 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Checking Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 16 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
    - Unionville Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 87)
      - Savings Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 11 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Xmas Club Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 11 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - School Savings Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 11 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Checking Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 11 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
    - West Haven Bank and Trust Company (Box 87)
      - Pd. Small Savings Accounts $10 and under, A-Z, 1952 December 12 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Large Savings Accounts over $10, cards and jackets, A-C, 1952 December 12 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Large Savings Accounts over $10, cards and jackets, D-Z, 1952 December 15 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
      - Checking Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 15 (Box 87, Reel Roll 2)
    - Windsor Locks Trust & Safe Deposit Company (Box 87)
      - Comm. Checking Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 15 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
      - Savings Accounts A-Z, 1952 December 15 (Box 87, Reel Roll 1)
  - Final file, undated; 1.5 inches (Box 88)
    Contains composite figures showing disposition of total liabilities, with drafts and work sheets.
    Alphabetical by bank.
  - Description of property in receivership offered for sale, 1945; 1 inch (Box 88)
  - Federal tax papers, 1945-1950; 1 inch (Box 88)
    Corporation and personal tax returns, withholding reports, etc.
  - Record of foreclosures, 1929-1937; .5 cubic feet (3 binders) (Box 89)
    Form summaries.
    Alphabetical by name of bank.
  - Correspondence concerning closed banks, 1929-1957; .5 cubic feet (Box 90)
    Includes material on banks liquidated prior to the 1935 statute.
  - Administrative papers of Liquidation Division, 1935-1960; 2.5 cubic feet (Box 91)
    - Bonding Company material (Box 91)
    - Forms, instructions, etc. (Box 92)
    - Checkbooks, 1944-1951 (Box 93)
    - Deposit books, 1939-1944 (Box 93)
    - Expense worksheets (Box 93)
    - Personnel and payroll records (Box 94)
    - Personnel and payroll records (Box 95)
    - Commissioner's signature plate (Box 95)
  - Safe Deposit Box Material, 2 cubic feet (Box 96-97)
    Documents and other valuables found in safe deposit boxes in closed banks.
    RESTRICTED.
- Series 2. Incorporation Files and Special Charters, circa 1913-1957; 4 cubic feet
  - American Bank & Trust Company, Bridgeport (Box 98)
    Organized under Special Law.
    Closed 1933 August 30.
  - American Industrial Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 98)
    Organized under General Law.
  - American Trust Company, Bristol (Box 98)
  - Ansonia Bank and Trust Company (Box 98)
    Name later changed to People's Bank & Trust Company.
    Application denied 1924 July 17.
  - Bankers Trust Company, Essex (Box 98)
    Merged with and into the Riverside Trust Company, Hartford, 1958 July 16.
  - Bankers Trust Company, Hartford (Box 98)
    Consolidated with Hartford National Bank & Trust Company, 1933 December 9.
  - Bankers Trust Company, Norwich (Box 98)
  - Bridgeport Industrial Bank (Box 98)
    Formerly Italian Credit Association, Inc.
    Restraining order issued 1931 September 10. Receiver discharged and corporation dissolved 1933 April 7.
  - Bridgeport Trust Company (Box 98)
  - Bristol-American Bank and Trust Company (Box 98)
    Consolidated with American Trust Company, Bristol
  - Bristol-American Bank and Trust Company (Box 98)
    Purchase of Bristol Trust Company.
  - Bristol Trust Company (Box 98)
    Sold to Bristol-American Bank & Trust Company on 1931 December 31.
  - Broadway Bank and Trust Company, New Haven (Box 98)
    Closed 1931 December 23.
  - Capitol State Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 98)
  - Central Industrial Bank, Waterbury (Box 98)
    Final certificate of dissolution filed 1938 July 19.
  - Central Trust Company, Norwalk (Box 98)
  - Cheshire Bank and Trust Company (Box 98)
    Closed 1931 September 31.
  - Citizens Bank & Trust Company, East Norwalk (Box 98)
    Organized under Geneal Law.
    Application denied 1929 December 16.
  - Citizens Industrial Bank, New Britain (Box 98)
    Application denied 1928 April 19.
  - City Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 98)
    Closed 1932 January 1
  - City Industrial Bank, Bridgeport (Box 98)
    Formerly City Loan Corporation.
  - Columbus Bank and Trust Company, New Haven (Box 98)
    Merged with Community Bank & Trust Company, New Haven, 1932 October 31.
  - Commercial Bank and Trust Company, Bridgeport (Box 98)
  - Commercial Trust Company, New Britain (Box 98)
    Closed 1930 December 12.
  - Community Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 98)
    Application denied 1927 January 18.
  - Congress Bank and Trust Company, New Haven (Box 98)
    Closed 1931 December 30.
  - Connecticut River Banking Company, Hartford (Box 98)
    Merged with Travelers Bank & Trust Company, Hartford, both of which banks simultaneously merged with and into the Hartford National Bank & Trust Company effective 1954 November 1.
  - Cos Cob Trust Company (Box 98)
    Application denied 1926 August 19
  - Danbury Trust Company (Box 98)
    Application denied 1927 September 15.
  - Danielson Trust Company (Box 98)
    Closed 1931 December 18. Reopened 1933 May 22. Taken over by Windham County National Bank on 1934 May 28.
  - Devon Bank & Trust Company (Box 98)
    Taken over by Milford Trust Company on 1930 March 12.
  - East Hampton Bank & Trust Company (Box 98)
    Closed 1936 July 16.
  - East Hartford Trust Company (Box 98)
    Closed 1932 January 2. Repoened 1933 January 23. Consolidated with and into Hartford National Bank and Trust Company 1950 May 17.
  - East Haven Bank & Trust Company (Box 99)
    Not organized. Service replaced by East Haven branch of First National Bank and Trust Company, New Haven, 1947 April 2.
  - East Haven Bank & Trust Company (Box 99)
    Taken over by First National Bank & Trust Company, New Haven, 1932 February 29.
  - East Haven Bank & Trust Company (Box 99)
    Application denied 1923 April 11.
  - Enfield Bank and Trust Company, Thompsonville (Box 99)
    Application denied 1920 June 3.
  - Enfield Bank and Trust Company, Thompsonville (Box 99)
    Application denied 1931 May 18.
  - Etna Industrial Bank, Bridgeport (Box 99)
    Application denied 1928 December 3.
  - Fairfield County Bank and Trust Company, Norwalk (Box 99)
  - Fairfield Trust Company (Box 99)
    Merged with Bridgeport City Trust Company, 1937 June 1.
  - Fidelity Industrial Bank, New Britain (Box 99)
    Merged with and into New Britain Trust Company on 1956 March 28 and continued as a branch.
  - Fidelity Trust Company, Hartford (Box 99)
  - Financial Industrial Bank, Bridgeport (Box 99)
    Notice of Intention to Organize never officially filed.
  - Greenwich Trust and Title Company (Box 99)
  - Guaranty Bank and Trust Company, Bridgeport (Box 99)
    Merged with Bridgeport City Trust Company on 1931 December 17.
  - Hamden Bank and Trust Company (Box 99)
    Closed 1931 December 17.
  - Hartford Morris Plan Company (Box 99)
    Authority to become an industrial bank under the name of The Morris Plan Bank of Hartford granted by Banking Commission on 1919 July 17.
  - Home Bank and Trust Company, Darien (Box 99)
    Merged with the Stamford Trust Company, effective 1950 September 29.
  - Home Bank and Trust Company, Greenwich (Box 99)
  - Home Bank and Trust Company, South Manchester (Box 99)
    Merged with Manchester Trust Company on 1932 January 4.
  - Home Bank and Trust Company, West Haven (Box 99)
    Merged with West Haven Bank and Trust COmpany on 1931 March 26.
  - Industrial Bank of Bridgeport, Organized under General Law.; Application denied 1926 November 1 (First application). (Box 99)
  - Industrial Bank of Bridgeport, Organized under General Law.; Application denied 1927 June 2 (Second application). (Box 99)
  - Industrial Bank of Commerce, Middletown (Box 99)
    Formerly known as The Morris PLan Bank of Middletown. Terminated 1934 September 11 upon sale of assets to The Industrial Sexurities Corporation.
  - Industrial Bank of Hartford, Inc. (Box 99)
    Voluntarily liquidated on 1943 June 14.
  - Industrial Bank of Norwalk (Box 99)
  - Italian Bank and Trust Company, Waterbury (Box 99)
    Organization never completed..
  - Italian Credit Association, Bridgeport (Box 99)
    Name changed to Bridgeport Industrial Bank in 1927. See entry for the latter bank.
  - Jefferson Trust Company, Putnam (Box 99)
  - Killingly Trust Company, Danielson (Box 99)
  - Lincoln Bank & Trust Company, New Haven (Box 99)
    Organization never completed.
  - Litchfield County Trust Company, Torrington (Box 99)
    Organization never completed, but combined with the Torrington Trust Company, 1916.
  - Merchants Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 99)
    Formerly Citizens Bank & Trust Company, Hartford.
  - Merchants Trust Company, Waterbury (Box 99)
    Merged with People's Bank & Trust COmpany, Waterbury, 1931 April 2, with the Merchants Trust Company as the resulting coporation. Closed 1931 December 23.
  - Meriden Industrial Loan Company (Box 99)
    Formerly known as Meriden Industrial Bank, Inc.
  - Meriden Loan Company (Box 99)
    Application denied 1928 December 4.
  - Middletown Trust Company (Box 99)
    Merged with Central National Bank, Middletown, 1944 August 5.
  - Milford Trust Company (Box 99)
    Liquidated on 1955 July 8 as the result of the sale of assets to the First National Bank & Trust Company, New Haven.
  - Moosup Bank and Trust Company (Box 99)
  - Moosup Trust Company (Box 99)
  - Morris Plan Bank of Bridgeport (Box 100)
    Acquired by Bridgeport City Trust Company on 1944 March 20.
  - Morris Plan Bank of Hartford (Box 100)
    Final Certificate of Dissolution filed 1940 November 30.
  - Morris Plan Bank of New Haven (Box 100)
    Merged with the New Haven Bank, N.B.A., on 1955 October 1.
  - Morris Plan Bank of Waterbury (Box 100)
    Formerly known as The Waterbury Morris Plan Company.
  - Mutual Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 100)
    Originally charted under name of The Audit and Guaranty Company, which name was changed to The Industrial Realty, Title & Guaranty Company on 1909 March 30.
    Formerly The Industrial realty, Title & Guaranty Company. Mutual Bank & Trust Company taken over by the City Bank & Trust Company 1930 November 8.
  - Mystic Bank and Trust Company, Mystic (Box 100)
    Application denied 1919 February 18.
  - Mystic Savings and Trust Company (Box 100)
  - Naugatuck Bank and Trust Company (Box 100)
  - Naugatuck Bank of Commerce (Box 100)
    Closed on 1931 October 7.
  - Naugatuck Valley Morris Plan Bank, Ansonia (Box 100)
    Formerly Naugatuck Valley Morris Plan Company.
    Final dissolution effected on 1937 December 21.
  - New Canaan Trust Company (Box 100)
    Application denied 1929 May 7.
  - Newfield Bank and Trust Company, Bridgeport (Box 100)
    Merged with First National Bank, Bridgeport, 1931 December 17.
  - New Hartford Trust Company (Box 100)
    Merged with Riverside Trust Company, Hartford, 1955 September 30.
  - New London Morris Plan Company (Box 100)
  - New London Trust & Safe Deposit Company (Box 100)
  - North End Bank and Trust Company, Bridgeport (Box 100)
    Merged with and into the Brideport City Trust Company, effective 1939 January 3.
  - Norwalk Industrial Bank, South Norwalk (Box 100)
    Application denied 1929 March 28.
  - Orange Bank and Trust Company, West Haven (Box 100)
  - Park City Industrial Bank, Bridgeport (Box 100)
  - Park Street Trust Company, Hartford (Box 100)
    Merged with and into Phoenix State Bank & Trust Company, Hartford, effective 1950 September 15.
  - Pawcatuck Bank and Trust Company, Stonington (Box 100)
    Closed 1932 July 13.
  - People's Bank and Trust Company, Branford (Box 100)
    Liquidated 1947 March 26.
  - People's Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 100)
    Application denied 1920 October 1.
  - People's Bank and Trust Company, Waterbury, Organized under General Law.; Merged witrh Merchants Trust Company, Waterbury, 1931 April 2. (Box 100)
  - People's Trust Company, Norwalk, Organized under Special Law.; Closed 1931 November 2. (Box 100)
  - People's Trust Company, Stamford (Box 100)
    Application denied 1923 January 24.
  - Phoenix State Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 100)
    Merged with and into the Hartford Connecticut Trust Company, effective 1954 July 1, as a result of which the name of this bank was changed to the Connecticut Bank & Trust Company.
  - Portland Trust Company (Box 100)
    Consolidated with the Riverside Trust Company on 1950 August 4, at which time its existence was terminated.
  - Putnam Bank and Trust Company (Box 100)
  - Rockville Bank (Box 100)
    The Rockville National Bank liquidated and resumed its corporate franchise as a state bank on 1933 December 12.
  - Salem Trust Company, Naugatuck (Box 101)
  - Salisbury Bank and Trust Company, Lakeville (Box 101)
    Incorporated as The Robbins Burrall Trust Company. The Savings Society of Salisbury authorized to transfer its assets to the trust company, and the latter authorized to change its name in 1925.
  - Security Trust Company, Hartford (Box 101)
  - Shelton Bank and Trust Company (Box 101)
  - Shelton Trust Company (Box 101)
    Consolidated with First National Bank & Trust Company, Bridgeport, 1950 December 2.
  - Sons of Italy Industrial Bank, New Haven (Box 101)
    Dissolved in 1932.
  - South End Trust Company, South Norwalk (Box 101)
  - South Norwalk Trust Company (Box 101)
    Merged with and into the Bridgeport City Trust Company, effective 1957 August 5.
  - Southport Savings Bank (Box 101)
    Merged with and into the Bridgeport People's Savings Bank, 1955 July 1.
  - Springdale Bank and Trust Company, Stamford (Box 101)
    Acquired business of Stamford Industrial Bank in 1943 July. Merged with and into the Greenwich Trust Company, 1957 October 1.
  - Stamford Industrial Bank (Box 101)
    Business acquired by the Springdale Bank & Trust Company, Stamford, in 1943 July.
  - Terryville Bank and Trust Company (Box 101)
    Application denied 1924 September 2.
  - Thames Bank and Trust Company, Norwich (Box 101)
    Originally charted in 1825 as The President, Directors and Company of the Thames Bank. In 1865 it converted into a national banking association, known as the Thames National Bank. In 1929, said National Bank went into liquidation and the original Thames Bank resumed operations. On 1929 November 30, said Thames Bank and the Bankers Trust Company, Norwich, consolidated and continued business under the name and title of the Thames Bank & Trust Company.
  - Torrington Morris Plan Bank (Box 101)
    Application denied 1926 June 10.
  - Torrington Trust Company (Box 101)
    Change of name from Torrington Bank and Trust Company effected 1916 December 12.
  - Travelers Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 101)
    Merged with Connecticut River Banking Company into Hartford National Bank & Trust Company, effective 1954 November 1.
  - Trust Company of Old Greenwich (Box 101)
    Incorporated under name of the Union Trust Company of Greenwich. Name changed to the Home Bank and Trust Company in 1919. Name again changed to Sound Beach Trust Company in 1925. Name changed to Trust Company of Old Greenwich in 1931. Merged with and into the Stamford Trust Company effective 1957 May 31.
  - Unionville Bank and Trust Company (Box 101)
    Closed 1932 January 2.
  - United State Security Trust Company, Hartford (Box 101)
    Consolidation of the Security Trust Company, the United States Bank, and the Fidelity Trust Company.
  - Washington Bank and Trust Company, Bridgeport (Box 101)
    Application denied 1920 April 15.
  - Washington Industrial Bank, Bridgeport (Box 101)
    Application withdrawn two days before hearing thereon, which was ordered to take place on 1928 October 18.
  - Waterbury Trust Company (Box 101)